Hace varios últimos años tenemos
Between the
En raíz deANDbijanc
está la
cataria.
S 다양한
en muchos años.
También en los próximos años,
vemos a la visión de los potenciales de crecimiento
en varios sectores,
particularmente en los sectores de consumidores
o el sector FMCG,
incluyendo las industrias de producción de comida
y beverage.
En realidad, vemos el potencial de crecimiento
más grande para nuestras soluciones de encodimiento
y marcando de una perspectiva global.
Con esto en mente,
el mercado de encodimiento y marcando
es de la importancia estratégica más alta
para el livrador
y estamos enfocando todos nuestros esfuerzos
en seguir expandiendo la posición del livrador
y las fuerzas en este área.
En este contexto,
los investimientos significativos
han sido realizados en el pasado
y van a seguir realizando en los próximos años.
Esto envuelve los investimientos
en nuestra presencia global.
Mientras tenemos una subsidiaría en los Estados Unidos since 1974,
hemos establecido un centro de competencia
en China en 2022.
En paralelo,
hemos expandido nuestra red mundial
de compañías de negociación.
Estos grandes pasos fueron acompañados
por más investimientos en salas y marketing.
Estamos seguros de que solo podemos ser
succesivos en nuestra industria
si entendemos a nuestros clientes
los desafíos y los necesarios
en las diferentes aplicaciones mejor
que a nadie más.
Solo podemos darles a nuestros clientes
con el beneficio más alto posible.
Para hacer esto,
es el elemento que vemos
en las aplicaciones específicas
y en los desafíos en detalle.
En términos de una solución comprensiva
para el producto, coden y marcando,
esto también significa
que podemos ofer
alta calidad de ingres
para una gran cantidad de aplicaciones.
Y estamos succesivos en hacer esto
muy suficientemente.
En 2021,
hemos fortalecido
nuestras experiencias
en el área de ingeniería de ingres
por establecer nuestra propia
investigación y desarrollo
laboratorio en el estado de equipamiento de arte.
La expansión de competencia
también ha llevado a la adquisición
de solución de ingres
y la integración
en la organización o grupo.
Desde entonces,
hemos estado empujando
con el desarrollo más alto
de una gran variedad de tipos de ingres
especialmente para las aplicaciones desafíos.
Porque entendemos
que solo podemos lograr
un resultado perfecto
cuando tecnología y ingres
trabajan perfectamente.
Así que,
estamos bien posicionados
para darles el mejor coden
y marcando sistemas disponibles,
siempre considerando
la mejor solución posible
para nuestros clientes.
Y cuando digo
nosotros,
estoy hablando principalmente de vosotros,
nuestros compañeros de trabajo
y experiencias del mundo.
Sin tus pasos y experiencias,
no pudimos lograr esto.
Solo con vosotros
podemos dar máximo beneficio
a nuestros clientes,
distribuir la solución correcta
a los muchos desafíos
que veremos en el futuro.
Y para esto,
me gustaría agradecerles
muy sinceramente
por su apoyo
y tu colaboración
para tu dedicación
y pasión
en tu trabajo de día a día
con nuestros clientes.
Me gustaría agradecerles
a nuestros clientes
que nos han acompañado aquí hoy.
Siempre hemos ayudado
y apoyado a desarrollarnos más
más.
Trabajamos,
ofertamos tus desafíos
y nos permitimos
desarrollar nuevas soluciones.
Por favor, a todos mis colegas,
me gustaría agradecerles
muy mucho
por estas grandes colaboraciones.
Gracias.
Ladies and gentlemen,
como pueden ver,
no tendríamos ni idea
si nos justizamos
y nos congratulamos
a nosotros
en nuestros sucesos.
En cooperación
con nuestros compañeros
y en una coordinación
con los clientes,
nuestros expertos
han intensivamente
explorado
los trens significativos
que forman
el futuro
de la industria de packaging
y la manufacturación de los productos.
Como nos progresamos
durante el XXI.
Centro,
estamos creciendo
un demando más
para las soluciones
de la packaging.
El riesgo de automación
y digitalización
y procesos de producción.
Y el impacto
de las escuelas laborales
en nuestras industrias.
Los manufacturadores
ahora investen
en materiales innovativos
y están enfocando
en reducir
sus colegas
para los precios
para los demandos
evolucionados.
Primero
y foremost,
el tren
contra la sustanibilidad
se ha convertido
en un aspecto indispensable.
Consumores
y empresas
alike
están empujando
para materiales ecofriendos,
packaging
recyclable
y la reducción en el peso.
Este riesgo
se ha convertido
no solo
en conservencias mentales
pero también
por las presiones
regulatorias
y el avance
de los impactos
de nuestras acciones
en el planeta.
Más sobre,
automación
y digitalización
están revolucionando
la landscapes de producción,
operaciones
y el avance de recursos
optimizados.
Advances
en robotics
y inteligencia artificiales
y las cosas internetas
están enviando
a las empresas
para monitorar
y controlar
sus procesos
con una presión
imprescindible
y
creer
la eficiencia
y reducir
los costos de producción.
Estas tecnologías
también se mitigan
los efectos
de la escuelta laboral
de automación
de tareas complexas
y traer
nuevos trabajadores
a un precio más rápido.
La escuelta laboral
de la escuelta
se ha convertido
en un issue
crítico
en el packaging
y en los sectores de manufactura
con un impacto
significativo
en ambos
cruces
y innovaciones.
Estas empresas
están creviendo
con una fuerza de trabajo
y un poco
de talento
entrando en la industria.
Esta escuelta
se ha accesorizado
por el precio rápido
de los avances tecnológicos
requeriendo
trabajadores
para procesar
una escuelta laboral
que incluye
tanto
la creación tradicional
y
la proficiencia digital.
La escuelta laboral
se ha convertido
en esta fuerza
y no solo en el que
sus clientes
se adaptan
y rechazan
esta escuelta laboral
pero también contribúan
a un futuro más
sustaino
y equitable
para todo el futuro.
Como siempre
hemos estado prensas
en la escuelta laboral
explorando nuevas
formas de hacer
coden
y marcar
más simple,
más flexibles
y más eficientes.
Y durante este tiempo
hemos nunca perdido
la escuelta laboral
más valiente
de la escuelta laboral.
En otros casos
hemos estado
procurando
soluciones
para encontrar
los desafíos
del futuro.
¡Inteligencia!
High expectations
lead to extraordinary solutions.
Solutions that follow a vision
not a path.
Solutions
that are smarter,
better,
more intelligent.
Our aspiration
is to provide
best possible
customer solutions.
Simplify operation,
ensuring quality,
secure efficiency.
Every lightninger is designed
with this aspiration in mind.
Intelligence.
That's the vision
for which we are pioneers.
This is precisely why we focus
our research and development
activities on intelligence early on.
We were the first in our industry
to do so,
to further expand
our technological leadership.
We invented intelligent technology
and have succeeded
in developing it
into cutting edge products
that really make a difference.
For many years we have been generating
significant customer benefit
thanks to intelligent technology.
Not for the sake of technology,
but technology that delivers
the right solution
when you need them.
Technology that makes coding
and marking easier
and ensures real efficiency
and productivity,
which is what customers
demand and expect
for their day-to-day operations.
Ladies and gentlemen,
once again,
the time has come for us
to take another pioneering step.
We have listened to our customers
very closely.
We have analyzed and understood
what drives them.
We have visited our customers
and tuned into their needs.
We have recognized their challenges.
We have also conducted extensive research
and parallel to all this,
we searched for new technologies
and sent out our engineers
and applicant consultants
on a clear mission
to set an all new standard.
We questioned basically everything
because if you really want
to set a new benchmark,
you must explore new ways of thinking,
thinking outside the box,
looking ahead,
assessing trends,
rejecting wrong paths with courage,
at times, taking detours.
Sometimes it comes down to taking
the good things
and making them even better.
And we have recognized
that to create something
entirely new and better,
we need to focus even more closely
on one very specific topic
in our research and development.
Intelligence.
Real intelligence
that delivers more simplicity,
more efficiency
and more flexibility.
In short,
much more customer benefit
and a lot more excited
inspired customers.
This is exactly
what we have accomplished.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the time has finally come.
Today, here and now,
you will experience
the most intelligent printing technology
in the world.
Experience our new
live-agent coding and marking system,
the new world standard.
www.mooji.org
Ladies and gentlemen,
here they are,
the new intelligence coding
and marking systems from the library.
First and only ones of their time,
the new Leibinger IQJet.
This is where tremendous application knowledge
meets the art of engineering.
With the IQJet from Leibinger,
we are introducing an all-new generation
of intelligent coding and marking systems.
And they are geared towards a single goal,
to offer our customers
the greatest possible benefit
in day-to-day use.
Or to put it even more simply,
to offer more than everyone else.
And to us, this means
giving our customers the confidence
that everything is functioning smoothly
around the clock
when coding and marking their products.
Providing our customers with the easiest to use
coding and marking systems available today
to always offer our customers
those cost-effective solutions
for all their applications
to help achieve sustainability goals
by providing the smallest
carbon footprint products
along with a peace of mind
and satisfaction
of no longer having to worry
about coding and marking their products.
With the new Leibinger IQJet,
we have succeeded in achieving that.
So, let's take a closer look
at the IQJet.
So, from the exterior you can
can't help but notice
the streamlined, timeless design
with the large 10.1 inch touch display
and the new print head
which now prints more content
with up to 48 dots
and therefore up to 8 lines of code.
But the real assets
and outstanding features
are on the inside of the new IQJet.
And this is where four intelligent
assistance systems
work together to solve
the major challenges
of coding and marking products.
Not only in a way that is different
ladies and gentlemen, but also
much better than all the others.
So, let me briefly introduce
to you these four
very unique systems,
assistance systems.
First, IQ print.
The plug and print
functionality. Responsible
for everything that guarantees
excellent print quality
and the high availability
of the IQJet at all times.
Second, smart OS.
Responsible for the easy operation
and integration of the IQJet
into the production line.
Third, smart efficiency.
Which ensures the lowest operating costs
in the industry.
And fourth,
smart care.
Which means that you won't
have to maintain the IQJet
for five years.
Yes, you heard me right.
No maintenance for five years,
but more on that later.
So, I will now take a few minutes
to go into detail about each
of the intelligent assistance systems
so that you can understand
the unique technologies behind them.
So, I will start with IQ print.
As mentioned earlier,
this intelligent assistance
is responsible for
consistently excellent print quality.
The quickest start-up times
and extremely robust printing technology.
IQ print guarantees
maximum productivity in day-to-day operation.
But, how is this possible?
You may ask.
The unique nozzle seal
not only closes the nozzle,
but also the gutter
and the entire ink return,
sealing them completely airtight.
This creates a hydraulic,
odd airtight hydraulic circuit,
which is the prerequisite
for automatic circulation
of the ink through the entire system.
And it ensures that blockages
in the ink circuit or ink drying
are virtually impossible.
For our customers,
this means an exceptionally reliable system
that is available to the maps.
It starts up quickly when it's needed.
There is no ink spitting
as commonly experienced with other systems.
And perhaps best of all,
there is no need to clean
or flush the printhead
of the ink cycle,
as is the case with conventional inkjet printers,
neither at start-up or at shutdown.
But that's not all.
In addition to all these advantages,
the new IQ print is also significantly more robust
and therefore failsafe for many years to come.
The ink circuit closes and opens
40% faster than before,
so the IQ jet is ready to print even more quickly.
This ensures maximum availability
and reliability of the IQ jet
in its day-to-day use.
Of course, the new nozzle sealing technology
and automatic ink circulation
are also a key to consistent print quality.
But IQ jet or IQ print
has even more to offer in this regard.
The new ink temperature control
keeps the ink temperature in the printhead
consistently at the right level.
At the same time,
the viscosity of the ink is precisely controlled,
thanks to a separate ink mixing tank
with a very small control volume
in conjunction with advanced algorithms.
Viscosity control is now much more dynamic,
much faster and more precise
than with any conventional CIJ printer,
where viscosity is usually controlled
in the large reservoir,
control much more sluggish
and slower than with the IQ jet.
With IQ print,
the intelligent ink management system,
you no longer have to worry about print quality.
The IQ jet prints in the very best quality
immediately after start-up.
It continues to do so until the end of production
or even around the clock.
Expensive rejects or complaints are things of the past.
This is what we mean by maximum customer benefit
and it is precisely why we developed IQ print.
So, moving on to the next intelligent
assistance function, SMART OS.
OS stands for Operating System
and this function is responsible
for the simple, intuitive operating system
as well as the easy integration of the IQ jet
into the production environment.
Let's take a closer look.
The new IQ jet is operated
via a large, high-resolution 10.1-inch touch display.
The capacitive touch technology
enables the same operability
you benefit from with a smartphone,
i.e. with easy swiping, dragging, dropping, or zooming.
The display is very responsive,
it is promptly reacting to any finger touch.
When developing the operating concept
we were inspired by state-of-the-art standards
in design thinking and in user-centered design.
It is intuitively simple
and offers quick access to all key functions
and data at all times.
All essential information is clearly displayed
on the home screen
and this means that the operator
normally has no need to change the menu
and can always work in the familiar home screen.
The large, color-coordinated operating elements
make it easy to read the current status of the IQ jet.
The new remote screening
is a case-dependent screensaver
that displays the current status of the IQ jet
and the product counters in full-screen mode
working according to the traffic light principle
like a signal map.
Green indicates that the IQ jet is running,
red the IQ jet has a malfunction
and blue the IQ jet is paused.
This makes it easy to see everything that is important
even from a distance
saving operators a few trips back and forth.
The central menu
in the lower part of the display
with only five icons
is used for general navigation.
From there you can access all main functions
and return to the previous menu at any time.
This makes it easy to find all relevant content
and functions.
The print job editor
has also been improved in great detail.
Numerous design or numerous templates
and design functions are now available.
This allows you to create print jobs
tailored to your specific needs
in no time at all
and to start them simply by the touch of a button.
And if an operating function is not quite clear to you,
Smart OS offers so-called tool tips
or also known as mouseovers or quick info.
So the tool tip appears
when the finger remains motionless
for a short time on the respective element
and provides a brief description of the function.
Our operating philosophy is very simple.
We want anyone to be able to work with our IQJet
without the need for manual or operator training.
So Smart OS ensures even more operating reliability
with myDisplay.
MyDisplay allows you to adapt the operations
specifically to the needs of the respective user
with just a few clicks
all the required settings are made
and the user only sees what he or she really needs
to complete his or her specific tasks
for instance changing the print job.
Everything else is simply hidden.
MyDisplay is a great tool
that helps to virtually eliminate operating errors.
No less important when investing in a coding and marking system
is ease with which it can be integrated
into the production environment.
Here too Smart OS has a lot to offer.
The IQJet features a signal monitor
for the clear display of all input and output signals
as well as a signal simulation function.
So this valuable signal visualization tool
for all input and output
makes it easy to integrate the IQJet
into a production line.
For example signals wired to the inputs
can be visualized
and you can immediately see
whether a signal is present or not.
This means that correct wiring
and signal reliability can be quickly checked.
Moreover output signals can also be temporarily set
by the IQJet to test the external wiring
without the need for a multimeter
or oscilloscope.
The integrated PLC,
the Programmable Logic Controller
is also new.
It enables the convenient linking
of input signals via drag and drop.
All this without requiring any programming knowledge
and without additional external hardware
or extra wiring work.
With the integrated PLC,
printer functions and peripheral devices
can be triggered or controlled individually
depending on input or output signals.
The OPC-UA interface is also available
from now on.
OPC-UA is considered the interface standard
for industry 4.0.
The OPC-UA
detailed process data
from a wide variety of machine control types
can be read, displayed
and analyzed in real time.
Traditional communication barriers
are now in the past.
Today virtually all PLC,
machine and control manufacturers
support this standard.
So connecting new production equipment
no longer takes days
but is usually carried out in less than an hour.
Integrating the printhead
into a production line
is also made easier than ever
thanks to the new bus-based communication
in the IQJET.
The printhead umbilical
is more flexible and adaptable.
This means that even the tightest
installation conditions are no longer a problem
and the printhead can be placed
in optimal position
within the manufacturing process.
So let me summarize all the key features
of the intelligent SMART OS function.
SMART OS makes operating the IQJET
simple, fast and absolutely reliable.
Any possible user operating errors
are reduced to a minimum.
All important functions are clearly organized
and selected without time-consuming navigation
in the operating menu.
The IQJET can be operated by anyone
right from the work-go.
There is no need for user training.
A big advantage is the simple integration
of the IQJET into any production environment.
Many available interfaces
and an integrated PLC
make everything quicker and easier
than ever before.
And when the IQJET is fully connected
you can test everything with the help
of the signal monitor
and the system is ready to go into operation.
Complicated was yesterday
and today is all about ease of use.
And this is exactly what we mean
by unmatched customer benefit.
So let's turn our attention
to the third intelligent assistant.
SMART EFFICIENCY.
SMART EFFICIENCY
ensures that the operating costs
of the IQJET
are reduced to an absolute minimum.
That resources and the environment
are respected
and that the user's well-being
is taken care of.
Let me show you how all this is possible.
With the integrated solvent recovery
evaporated solvent is condensed
from the mixing tank
and the ink return line
recovered back into the system.
SMART EFFICIENCY
also includes a one-of-a-kind eco mode.
The additional savings effects
made possible by this unique functionality
of the IQJET
should not be underestimated.
And Leibinger is the only one
who could offer this functionality.
Think of it like the engine start-stop functionality
that is now included on almost all cars.
When the IQJET is not in use
the ink circuit closes automatically
after a predetermined time.
This means that no solvent can evaporate
and escape into the environment.
SMART EFFICIENCY reduces
solvent consumption by up to 50%.
And this of course has a direct
and very positive impact
on operating costs.
Also, significantly less solvent
is released into the environment
for much better working conditions
and the best possible protection
of employee health and well-being.
SMART EFFICIENCY
not only minimizes solvent consumption
but it also saves a considerable amount of energy.
All components of the IQJET
are designed for lowest energy consumption.
The intelligently controlled pump
plays a major role here
as it is only operated intermittently.
Unlike conventional printers
where the pump runs continuously
with the IQJET it only switches on briefly
to fill a pressure tank.
This reduces the energy consumption
of the pump to a minimum
and it also maximizes the durability of the pump.
Thanks to SMART EFFICIENCY
the IQJET consumes only 36 watts on average.
Conventional printers need many times that.
The IQJET boasts the lowest energy consumption
on the market.
Now, moving on to our entirely new cartridge system
and I can rightly say
the best cartridge system in our industry.
Why?
Because no other system is easier,
no other system is quicker to replace
and no other system saves as much anything.
The new XXL cartridges can hold 950 milliliters
which means very large refills of ink and solvent.
If necessary, the quick loading system
allows the cartridges to be inserted
without getting mixed up.
This means that the ink and solvent cartridges
can only fit into the respective refill slot.
The type of consumable is also automatically checked
for consistency before refilling
and the operator is warned of any incorrect filling.
Thanks to the front access
and the special cartridge design
refilling the IQJET is quicker, easier
and more convenient than ever
and of course also during ongoing printing operation.
As mentioned earlier, changing cartridges is very easy
but to make it possible for anyone to do it
without training and interactive assistant
guides the operator through the process step by step.
Another new feature is that the cartridges
can be reordered via the integrated shop system
and added convenience in day-to-day operation.
Once the cartridges have been inserted,
the fluid is immediately emptied
into the internal storage tanks.
This extends the reserve runtimes to up to 50 hours
enough time to order consumables
even after the refill message on the display.
When I say emptied, I mean totally emptied.
Unlike most conventional CIG printers
where considerable amounts of ink remain in the cartridges,
our XXL cartridges empty down to the last drop of ink.
This saves money and the cartridges can simply be disposed of
in the residual waste,
otherwise it becomes expensive hazardous waste.
I'd like to summarize what makes
the smart efficiency intelligence assistance function so unique.
Smart efficiency saves our customers money every day.
The IQJETs operating costs are the lowest in the industry,
up to 50% less solvent consumption,
low energy costs,
and, very importantly,
the environment and the operator are protected
to the greatest possible extent.
Moreover, the new cartridge system
saves a lot of ink due to complete emptying
and the reserve runtimes of consumables
are an incredible 50 hours.
I don't like repeating myself, but I will anyway.
This is what we mean by maximum customer benefit.
We have talked about reducing operating costs to a minimum.
Now I would like to move on to the last of the four intelligent functions.
Thanks to smart care,
the new Leibinger IQJET needs no maintenance for five years.
That means five years printing, printing, printing with no maintenance.
This is achieved thanks to many technical innovations,
such as the new housing
with the increased protection against water and dust as standard,
use of the most durable and high quality components,
the new printhead with its precision parts
manufactured in the Leibinger production facilities
down to micron accuracy,
and the most intelligent hydraulic ink circulation system,
which ensures a much longer service life for the print pump and other components.
In addition, smart care offers the fully automated printhead refresh
at the touch of the button.
It removes ink related contamination from the printhead,
which could occur in extreme customer applications,
and it maintains the printhead in a safe and clean manner.
A fine spray solvent is directed from the gutter
to specific locations in the printhead.
The ink gutter moves up and down to remove any impurities.
Afterwards, a complete automatic drying takes place
and everything is impeccably clean and dry
without requiring any manual intervention
and without the operator coming into contact with cleaning fluid.
That is absolutely unique.
And when it's finally time for maintenance after five years,
customers are free to do it themselves if they wish.
Do it yourself or DIY maintenance is the catch word here.
And if we say this, we actually mean it.
Step by step, the operator is shown on the display
what they have to do.
Even unskilled workers can carry out the maintenance.
No special tools are necessary.
Yes, maintenance can be this easy with the IQJet.
Our customers greatly benefit from zero waiting times
for customer service, better planning,
and ultimately a real plus in production time.
Ladies and gentlemen, these four intelligent functions
make the IQJet the coding and marking system
with the lowest operating costs in the industry.
Let me give you a tangible example.
A manufacturer in the FMCG sector
with 5,000 production hours per year
and 400 prints per minute
with 20-character prints,
a typical application,
saves more than 1,360 euros in the first year alone.
Within eight years,
this adds up to almost 11,000 euros saved
compared to conventional Cij printers.
This makes the IQJet ideally suited
for cost-sensitive applications,
such as in the food and beverage sector
or in the FMCG segment in general.
It is the most versatile, cost-effective,
productive and durable coding and marking system in the world.
Finally, a coding and marking system
that gives customers consistent performance
without any intervention.
You install it and you almost forget.
Plug and print five years,
no maintenance in simply printing, printing, printing.
This is exactly what the four new
intelligent technologies were designed for
and what they guarantee.
Last but certainly not least,
I would like to briefly highlight
Liveanger Connect.
When the IQJet is connected to Liveanger Connect,
everything becomes easier
and, above all, even more efficient.
With Liveanger Connect,
the user is always well-informed
and has everything important in view,
whether the IQJet's current status,
previews of required actions such as
refill ink, the reach of consumables
or even the production output.
All information is displayed simply and clearly.
This also helps users react at an early stage
so that the production line does not come
to an unwanted standstill in the first place.
If wanted, the user can also be kept up to date
via push message, for example,
in the event of a malfunction.
In addition, historical data helps
identify and leverage any potential
for production optimization.
The modern cloud system is the
high performance platform
for all connected Liveanger printing systems,
regardless of whether they are connected
via LAN or cellular network.
Y, if required,
service partners can also be easily integrated.
They can access the IQJet data remotely
and provide targeted support
on all important service issues.
The use of Liveanger Connect
increases the productivity and efficiency
of all connected printers in day to day use
and provides the additional certainty
that everything is under control.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'm at the end of my presentation
and now I hope you enjoy
our new product video.
Thank you very much.
Every great idea begins with a clear starting point.
Here lies the power of change,
of innovation.
A thought begins its journey,
simple and ingenious.
And the unimaginable becomes reality.
Time and time again,
we at Liveanger challenge the conventions
of an entire industry
and create solutions that are simpler,
smarter, more intelligent.
Introducing the new IQJet,
the very first intelligent coding
and marketing system worldwide.
Trouble-free printing guaranteed.
No matter what shape,
no matter what surface.
With IQ Print,
the most intelligent ink management.
When not in use,
IQ Print automatically closes
the print nozzle
and lets the ink continue to circulate.
No dry out, no clogging.
Also thanks to Liveanger's
unique print and refresh function
which removes impurities
at the press of a button.
IQ Print ensures instant start-up
every time
and stable, high-quantity printing.
Easy to use with Smart OS,
the IQJet's intuitive operating concept,
individually adjustable
and clearly visible.
Printing has never been this easy
or this cost-effective
because Smart Efficiency
minimizes not only your energy consumption,
it also achieves up to 50%
salt and recovery,
protecting your health and the environment
and saving money.
Just like the XXL cartridges,
they are quickly replaced
and emptied down to the last drop.
And finally,
we're introducing Smart Care,
printing 5 years without maintenance.
The new IQJet.
Intelligence on point.
Good afternoon everybody.
My name is Christophe Lopez.
I joined Liveanger
as Chief Commercial Officer
at the beginning of March.
I'm really happy to be here today
to be able to meet you
our customers and our partners.
I've made many appointments
with many of you,
but if this is not the case,
don't hesitate to reach out to me.
If you want to talk,
I'll be more than happy to share
and spend time with you.
I've been in the marketing and coding industry
for nearly 15 years,
including 12 years with Marketing Match,
where I held a multiple executive position
in sales and marketing,
as well as general management
of the main site in France.
Before that,
I was already in the industry
working for Everyday Nissan
and Honeywell.
I decided to join Liveanger
because it is structurally different
from the rest of the competitors,
being a private company
with strong values
and a great innovative mindset.
I really see great potential
for development in the coming years.
I can also tell you
that being part of the company now,
I'm even more impressed
about the people, the technology
and the mindset.
I'm particularly impressed
by how Liveanger
is changing the game in CIG.
CIG is a great technology
when it was invented 40 years ago.
It rechained the game
at the time in the marketing and coding industry
by allowing the printing of valuable data
on a large variety of substrates
at high production speeds.
That was a revolution
to guarantee the trustability
and the freshness of products.
The issue of CIG
from the start
was that it was a complex
and not very reliable technology.
Printers would eventually not start
or would stop unexpectedly
o would spilling on the floor
and quality of prints
would vary over time.
It would also be quite costly to operate
using large quantities of fluid
and a lot of spare parts.
The main CIG manufacturers
tried to solve these problems
by implementing incremental enhancement
to reduce these issues
but none of them really addressed
the problem at the core
and instead they deployed armies of technicians
to maintain and repair the machines.
But this is history now
with the launch of IQChat.
How would you, customers and partners
define the ultimate
marking and coding machine?
I believe whether you are a production manager,
a quality manager, maintenance manager,
even a finance manager
what you want is one single thing.
You want a printer that you install easily
and then that will print seamlessly
as needed without having to intervene.
You install it and you almost forget it.
Productivity and low operating cost.
Albert Einstein said the definition of genius
is taking the complex
and making it simple.
IQChat is the first printer
that is really changing the game
since the invention of CIG
based on two unique features
which are simple to understand
and yet extremely complex to implement.
The number one concept
is that the head is sealed.
Let me take an image.
Look at that kind of paint.
If it's sealed,
it can stay perfect for many years
but just open the trap
and it will dry in only a few hours.
With live in your IQChat,
the ink will never dry
and the viscosity will stay stable
allowing perfect operation in all conditions.
I would like to take a second image.
This is what I call the balloon concept.
The way the in-circuit works in IQChat
is that you inflate once
and then you just need to bring a small quantity of air
to keep it inflated over time.
That means that the entire system
is working only a small fraction of the time
and why the reliability of IQChat is unmatched.
The competitor's machine,
even the most recent ones,
are continuously pumping
to maintain pressure in the in-circuit
and therefore their printers
are going to fail early.
Whatever they say or whatever they do.
With these two principles,
the IQChat printer redefines
the market standards for reliability
and autonomy in marking and coding.
Its unique disruptive design
will transform the industry's experience
working with CIG.
100% clean,
seamless start and stops,
5-year operation
without schedule maintenance
and un parallel cost of a machine.
Plug and print,
the ultimate printing machine.
This is the CIG we invented.
And now I would like to introduce
Christophe Orish,
our director of sales EMEA
and HAPAC,
that will tell you how we plan to work together with you
to turn this great innovation
into a huge commercial success.
Thank you very much.
Gracias, Christophe.
Good afternoon, ladies and gentlemen.
Now that you have seen the smartest coding
and marking system in the industry,
please give me the chance to talk to you
about the go-to-market strategy for this product
and some relevant tools
that will help you expand your business success
together with the Lighting On.
For us, the introduction of the completely new platform
represents an important milestone,
a massive technological step
with strategic importance.
And to this extent,
we would like you to benefit from the IQChat
as a partner and customer.
With the IQChat,
we will, on the one hand,
address existing, convinced customers,
as well as penetrate new markets
to sustainably grow our market share.
With its competitive price point
and in combination with the exceptionally low operating cost,
the IQChat is the ideal coding marking system
for a very broad range of applications
in virtually all segments of modern manufacturing.
With this in mind,
we would be working with you
to target new customer segments
and communicate the IQChat benefit message
with high-level impact.
We have started worldwide marketing activities
as of immediately,
and we are supporting this process
by professional communication measures.
This means stepping up social media communication
and newsletters,
participating in trade fairs around the globe,
international PR work,
benefit-focused campaigns and promotions,
a key account customer roadshow,
and, last but not least,
we will be going after our potential customers directly.
We also have attractive point-of-sale packages
ready for you,
as well as in brochures, data sheets,
and website content, of course,
which you can easily integrate into your website.
So, everything you need to successfully introduce
the IQChat is now available.
Of course, we are relying on you, our partners.
Because only together with you
will we be able to drive the marketing
of the IQChat forward,
and we will be supporting you wherever necessary
so that we can achieve these goals together.
We will begin training your sales teams immediately
so that they can effectively communicate
the many benefits of the IQChat.
We will also train your service staff
to ensure that the installation
and predictive maintenance of the IQChat
runs smoothly.
We will be letting you know today
when the training sessions will be held.
Right after this event,
you will also find out the exact price positioning
of the IQChat.
At the same time,
the price point is extremely attractive,
and when you consider the fact
that the IQChat has the lowest operating costs
in the industry
and includes many useful functions,
the package really is unbeatable.
Overall, a completely new benchmark
for total cost of ownership.
So, let me now briefly explain
what's next on today's agenda.
Following the presentation,
our complete team will be available
to answer any questions you may still have.
Of course, you will also have an opportunity
to experience the new IQChat,
the new marketing materials,
and much more life.
We have set up a small marketplace
in this room and in the adjoining room.
The various market stations
cover different relevant subjects
of the market launch of the IQChat.
You will receive more technical information,
general product information,
as well as marketing information.
A detailed marketplace guide,
including a map,
showing the different stations
is available at both sides
exit of this room.
So, everything that is required
for a successful launch.
Of course, you can also try out
the IQChat yourself
and familiarize with it.
Some refreshments and finger food
will be available for you there
and we will start serving those
in a couple of minutes.
In the further course,
we will have the main course buffet
set up around 4.30 pm
and we should not miss
the additional surprise afterwards.
So, we really look forward
to spending a few more hours
to celebrate this important milestone
and with food, drinks, music
and lively conversations.
We are very much looking forward
to sharing ideas with you
at our marketplace on the product,
the business and beyond.
So, finally, thank you very much
for your attention.